<user-guide>
  <project>Nox Information Bar</project>
  <topic>User Guide</topic>
  <version>3.0.0</version>
  <author>Gruma</author>
  <email>gruma@pobox.com</email>
  <section name="Description">
    <p>
      Nox Information Bar is an add-on for World of Warcraft that lets you
      display the game or character information important to you -
      continuously and in real-time.  Most other info bars give you a
      limited selection of data points you can turn on or off, but Nox 
      gives you exactly what you want to see, exactly the way you want to 
      see it.
    </p>
    <p>
      With the Nox Information Bar, you get the ability to customize both
      the data displayed on the bar itself, and in the tooltip displayed
      when you mouse over the bar.  Nox and its various bundled extensions
      give you a huge number of data points and optional formats to choose
      from, as well as any static text you want to configure.  All of this
      configuration can be done through a convenient GUI panel.
    </p>
    <p>
      Nox Information Bar comes to you courtesy of ins0mniaque, who created
      the original addon, and Gruma of Uther, who took over the addon when
      ins0mniaque became too busy to work on it.  We also have to extend
      thanks to the innumerable addon authors from whom we borrowed code, 
      ideas, and techniques, including Mairelon, Telo, the TitanMod team,
      and many, many others.
    </p>
  </section>
  <section name="Features">
    <p>
      Nox Information Bar has many great features built-in:
    </p>
    <feature-list>
      <feature>
        Slim, clean looks integrate with WoW without using unnecessary
        screen space.
      </feature>
      <feature>
        Sixteen fully customizable data slots.
      </feature>
      <feature>
        A fully customizable 30-line tooltip which by default displays
        experience stats similar to Telo's Clock, but can be
        configured to display anything you want.
      </feature>
      <feature>
        Experience bar overlays showing current and rested experience
        in a format easier to read than the default experience bar.
      </feature>
      <feature>
        Automatic resizing to accommodate the configured data.
      </feature>
      <feature>
        Complete mobility, allowing you to place the bar wherever you like,
        and optionally lock it in place once there.
      </feature>
      <feature>
        A GUI panel for customizing the bar, data slots, and tooltip.
      </feature>
      <feature>
        Compatibility with myAddOns.
      </feature>
      <feature>
        Clock offsets from server time configurable per-character for
        local time displays.
      </feature>
      <feature>
        Many configurable variables for everything from client 
        performance to character honor to combat to inventory and more.
      </feature>
      <feature>
        Optional format selectors for most variables to display them
        in various ways.
      </feature>
      <feature>
        Ability to configure plain text and colors in any display slot.
      </feature>
      <feature>
        Includes an optional addon to move many default GUI frames where
        you want them.
      </feature>
    </feature-list>
  </section>
  <section name="What's Included">
    <p>
      Nox Information Bar is delivered as several bundled and related
      addons.  Since every addon requires some of WoW's limited addon
      memory, and since some of these add background processing to the
      WoW client as things happen in the game world - even if their data
      isn't being displayed - packaging the addons like this lets you
      choose exactly which ones you want to have loaded.
    </p>
    <p>
      Nox Information Bar includes the following addons:
    </p>
    <addon-list>
      <addon name="NoxInformationBar">
        This includes the bar itself and many basic variables.
        This is required for most of the other addons to work.
      </addon>
      <addon name="NoxCombatStats">
        Adds combat-related information to the bar.
      </addon>
      <addon name="NoxEquipmentStats">
        Adds information about equipped items to the bar, including
        names, types, durability and repair costs.
      </addon>
      <addon name="NoxHonorStats">
        Adds honor-system information to the bar.
      </addon>
      <addon name="NoxMoneyExtension">
        Adds a coin display showing your current money, like the one
        at the bottom of the backpack.
      </addon>
      <addon name="NoxPlayerStats">
        Adds basic character and realm information to the bar.
      </addon>
      <addon name="NoxSkillStats">
        Adds information about your character's skills to the bar.
      </addon>
      <addon name="NoxMover">
        Allows you to move several UI frames around to make room for the
        bar - or just because you want to.  Can be used without the
        Nox Information Bar, but can only be configured using the bar's
        config panel.
      </addon>
      <addon name="NoxSampleExtension">
        Demonstrates how to write extension addons for Nox Information Bar,
        but adds no useful information by itself.
      </addon>
    </addon-list>
  </section>
  <section name="Installation">
    <p>
      To install, simply unzip the NoxInformationBar_vX.X.X.zip file into
      your <i>&lt;World of Warcraft&gt;</i>\Interface\AddOns directory.
      If you do not have the "Interface\AddOns" subdirectories in your game
      directory, create them before unzipping the Nox Information Bar.
    </p>
    <p>
      If you are already using an older version of the Nox Information Bar, I
      recommend deleting any old Interface\AddOns\Nox* subdirectories before
      unzipping the new file.  This will prevent conflicts with files and 
      addons that have been removed in the new version.
    </p>
  </section>
  <section name="Using The Bar">
    <p>
      Using the Nox Information Bar is easy - it doesn't <i>do</i> much
      other than show data.
    </p>
    <p>
      When you first load the bar, it will show up at the top of your
      screen displaying its default slots.  Hovering over the bar with
      the mouse pointer will bring up the tooltip, which also displays
      its default configuration at first.  Left click on the bar and
      hold the left mouse button down to drag the bar wherever you
      like on your screen.  Right click on the bar to bring up a brief
      menu.  This gives you the options of resetting the current
      session variables or of opening the configuration panel.  Move
      the mouse pointer off of the menu for a few seconds or hit the
      Esc key to close the menu without selecting an option.
    </p>
    <p>
      The background of the bar tracks your experience in your current
      level.  The purple bar shows your current experience earned, and the
      blue bar behind it shows how much experience you can earn while
      staying rested.  Once the purple bar passes the blue bar, you no
      longer earn rested experience until you rest again.  Once the purple
      bar fills the entire background, your character will progress to the
      next level and the both the blue and purple bars will reset to
      reflect your new level.
    </p>
    <p>
      Note that you cannot resize the Nox bar explicitly.  Instead you
      set the size of each of its display slots, and the bar will resize
      itself to fit them.
    </p>
  </section>
  <section name="Slash Commands">
    <p>
      Slash commands let you quickly control the look and behavior of the
      Nox bar.  Note that all of the functionality you can access through
      slash commands can also be accessed through the right-click menu
      or the configuration GUI.  Conversely, the configuration GUI can
      do some additional things that the slash commands cannot.
    </p>
    <slash>
      <desc>
        Show the configuration panel:
      </desc>
      <command>
        /noxib config
      </command>
    </slash>
    <slash>
      <desc>
        Show or hide the bar or individual slots:
      </desc>
      <command>
        /noxib show [slot=table]
      </command>
      <command>
        /noxib hide [slot=table]
      </command>
      <command>
        /noxib toggle [slot=table]
      </command>
    </slash>
    <slash>
      <desc>
        Lock the bar position:
      </desc>
      <command>
        /noxib lock
      </command>
      <command>
        /noxib unlock
      </command>
    </slash>
    <slash>
      <desc>
        Customize slot displays:
      </desc>
      <command>
        /noxib resize slot=table width=number
      </command>
      <command>
        /noxib remap slot=table display='string'
      </command>
    </slash>
    <slash>
      <desc>
        Reset the curent session statistics:
      </desc>
      <command>
        /noxib reset
      </command>
    </slash>
    <slash>
      <desc>
        Configure the tooltip:
      </desc>
      <command>
        /noxib tooltip [state=&lt;'on', 'off'&gt;] [position=&lt;'anchor'&gt;] [x=number] [y=number]
      </command>
    </slash>
    <slash>
      <desc>
        Configure the clock offset from server time:
      </desc>
      <command>
        /noxib clock [offsethour=number] [offsetminute=number]
      </command>
    </slash>
    <p>
      "table" parameters can be specified as:
    </p>
    <valuelist>
      <value name="numbers">"slot=1"</value>
      <value name="ranges">"slot=1-6"</value>
      <value name="lists">"slot=[ 1 3 7 8 ]"</value>
    </valuelist>
    <p>
      Display strings for the remap command (enclosed in single
      quotes) define what each slot will display. Variables in each
      display string (enclosed in braces) will be replaced in the bar
      with their current values.
    </p>
    <p>
      Anchor values for the tooltip can be:
    </p>
    <list>
      <value>'left'</value>
      <value>'topleft'</value>
      <value>'top'</value>
      <value>'topright'</value>
      <value>'right'</value>
      <value>'bottomright'</value>
      <value>'bottom'</value>
      <value>'bottomleft'</value>
      <value>'center'</value>
    </list>
    <subsection name="Examples">
      <example>
        <desc>
          Mark slots 4, 5 and 6 as visible
        </desc>
        <text>
          /noxib show slot=4-6
        </text>
      </example>
      <example>
        <desc>
          Display only the clock (in white) in a 100 pixel wide slot
        </desc>
        <text>
          /noxib hide slot=1-9
        </text>
        <text>
          /noxib show slot=1
        </text>
        <text>
          /noxib resize slot=1 width=100
        </text>
        <text>
          /noxib remap slot=1 display='|cffffffff{24hours}:{minutes}'
        </text>
      </example>
      <example>
        <desc>
         Display the current framerate in slot 6, followed by a space and 
         then "fps"
        </desc>
        <text>
          /noxib remap slot=6 display='{framerate} fps'
        </text>
      </example>
      <example>
        <desc>
          Put the tooltip in the bottom right corner
        </desc>
        <text>
          /noxib tooltip position='bottomright' x=-32 y=32
        </text>
      </example>
      <example>
        <desc>
          Shut off the tooltip
        </desc>
        <text>
          /noxib tooltip state='off'
        </text>
      </example>
      <example>
        <desc>
          Reset the clock offsets to zero
        </desc>
        <text>
          /noxib clock
        </text>
      </example>
      <example>
        <desc>
          Set the clock offset to minus 2 hours and 30 minutes
        </desc>
        <text>
          /noxib clock offsethour=-2 offsetminute=-30
        </text>
      </example>
    </subsection>
  </section>
  <section name="Customizing The Bar">
    <p>
      Both the main bar and the tooltip of the Nox Information Bar can
      be customized to show any information you want.  You do this by
      specifying <i>display strings</i> for the bar to show.
    </p>
    <subsection name="Display Strings">
      <p>
        Display strings determine what each element of the Nox bar will show.
        These are made of up any combination of variables, formats, color 
        codes and plain text.
      </p>
      <p>
        <i>Variables</i> are special words contained in
        braces that the Nox bar replaces at runtime with the actual values
        they represent.  Lists of the variables Nox recognizes are shown
        in the sections that follow.  If Nox does not recognize a variable,
        for instance if it is misspelled or simply not known, it will not
        replace the variable and it will instead show up exactly as entered
        on your screen.
      </p>
      <p>
        <i>Formats</i> are additional words placed inside the braces of a
        variable that alter the way the variables shows its value.  These
        can for instance be used to choose between integer and decimal
        number displays, or for other similar changes.  These are also
        listed later, after the variable sections.
      </p>
      <p>
        <i>Color codes</i> allow you to change the color and transparency of any
        text entered.  These will work for any variables or plain text,
        except for certain variables that automatically color themselves.
        These are explained in more detail later.
      </p>
      <p>
        <i>Plain text</i> is anything else you enter that is not a variable,
        color code, or format.  Nox always displays plain text exactly as
        you entered it.
      </p>
      <p>
        For example, in the display string:
      </p>
      <block>
        Time played: {timeplayed:short}
      </block>
      <p>
        "Time played: " is plain text, "{timeplayed}" is a variable,
        and "short" is a format that changes the way the {timeplayed} 
        variable displays.
      </p>
    </subsection>
    <subsection name="The Main Bar">
      <p>
        The main bar has sixteen display slots that you can turn on
        and off, resize, and configure independently.  Each slot gets
        its own display string which you specify.  You could configure
        Nox to show one variable in each slot, configure the entire
        bar to show only one slot with sixteen variables in it, or
        create any other configuration you choose.  The potential
        combinations are unlimited.
      </p>
    </subsection>
    <subsection name="The Tooltip">
      <p>
        The tooltip consists of 30 lines, each containing a left half and
        a right half.  A display string entered in the left half of a line
        will show up left-justified in the tooltip, and a display string
        in the right half will show up right-justified.  If the right half
        is left blank, then it will be ignored and the left half will
        fill the full width of the tooltip.
      </p>
      <p>
        To leave a blank line in the tooltip, put at least one space in the
        left display string and leave the right half empty.  If both halves
        of a line are empty, the tooltip will ignore the line entirely,
        and Nox will remove the line the next time you open the
        configuration GUI.  (This is an easy way to move the contents of the
        tooltip up - just blank the lines you don't want, close the config
        GUI and open it up again.  The blank lines will be gone.)
      </p>
      <p>
        Tooltip lines cannot be sized.  The tooltip will automatically size
        itself to fit the text it is showing at the time.
      </p>
    </subsection>
    <subsection name="Character-specific Overrides">
      <p>
        Nox allows each character to override specific groups of
        options, so that each character can share the common settings,
        can have their own settings, or any combination of the two.
        The four option groups that can be customized are the General
        options, the Clock settings, the Slot contents, and the
        Tooltip settings and contents.
      </p>
      <p>
        By default, all characters share one common set of settings.
        You can give a character private settings by checking the box
        for the appropriate group (or groups) in the
        "Character-specific Options" panel in the config GUI.  The
        common settings for that group will be copied over to the
        character, and you can start editing them immediately.
      </p>
      <p>
        To switch a character back to the common settings from
        customized settings, just uncheck the appropriate checkbox in
        the config GUI.  Note that if you make changes to customized
        settings and turn off the customization checkbox at the same
        time, the settings changes will <i>not</i> be saved.  Only the
        customization checkbox will be saved in that case.  If you
        want to change both in one edit session, turn off the checkbox
        first and then press the "Apply" button.  Your checkbox change
        will be saved, and the common settings will be loaded into the
        config GUI.  Now make your changes to the common settings and
        save them as normal.
      </p>
      <p>
        Note that the common settings are copied into the character's
        settings when you customize, but there is not yet a way to
        copy a character's custom settings to the common settings.
      </p>
    </subsection>
  </section>  
  <section name="Variables">
    <p>
      Variables provide data about the state of the game and your character.
      This section lists the variables that the Nox Information Bar and
      its extensions make available to you.
    </p>
    <subsection name="Variables provided by NoxInformationBar">
      <variable-list>
        <var>
          <code>{latency}</code>
          <desc>Current network latency in milliseconds.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{framerate}</code>
          <desc>Current framerate in frames per second.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{24hours}</code>
          <desc>Hours in current time in military format.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{hours}</code>
          <desc>Hours in current time.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{minutes}</code>
          <desc>Minutes in current time.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{ampm}</code>
          <desc>AM or PM of current time.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{x}</code>
          <desc>Current horizontal map location.</desc>
          <type>Number</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{y}</code>
          <desc>Current vertical map location.</desc>
          <type>Number</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{money}</code>
          <desc>Current amount of money owned.</desc>
          <type>Money</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{hpregen}</code>
          <desc>Current health regeneration rate.</desc>
          <type>Number</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{manaregen}</code>
          <desc>Current mana regeneration rate.</desc>
          <type>Number</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{hp}</code>
          <desc>Current health points.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{hploss}</code>
          <desc>Current health loss (max - current).</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{hp%}</code>
          <desc>Current health percentage.</desc>
          <type>Number</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{maxhp}</code>
          <desc>Maximum health.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{mana}</code>
          <desc>Current mana points.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{manaloss}</code>
          <desc>Current mana loss (max - current).</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{mana%}</code>
          <desc>Current mana percentage.</desc>
          <type>Number</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{maxmana}</code>
          <desc>Current mana loss (max - current).</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{xp}</code>
          <desc>Current experience points earned.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{xptolevel}</code>
          <desc>Additional XP needed to reach next level.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{xp%}</code>
          <desc>Current XP percentage earned towards next level.</desc>
          <type>Number</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{xptolevel%}</code>
          <desc>Percentage XP needed to level. (inverse of {xp%})</desc>
          <type>Number</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{maxxp}</code>
          <desc>Total XP to get to next level.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{rest}</code>
          <desc>
            Amount of "free" XP that is left to be earned for being rested.
          </desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{level}</code>
          <desc>Current level.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{ubs}</code>
          <desc>Used bag slots.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{abs}</code>
          <desc>Available bag slots.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{tbs}</code>
          <desc>Total bag slots.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{mem}</code>
          <desc>The current amount of UI memory used by addons.</desc>
          <type>Memory</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{restbonus}</code>
          <desc>
            Amount of additional experience that will be counted as "rested".
          </desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{restlimit}</code>
          <desc>
            Total amount of experience needed before the "rested" bonus is 
            used up.
          </desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{ammo}</code>
          <desc>Total amount of equipped ammo.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{sessionttl}</code>
          <desc>Estimated time to level for this session.</desc>
          <type>Time</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{levelttl}</code>
          <desc>Estimated time to level for this level.</desc>
          <type>Time</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{bestttl}</code>
          <desc>Smallest of session TTL and level TTL.</desc>
          <type>Time</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{totaltime}</code>
          <desc>The total amount of time played for this character.</desc>
          <type>Time</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{sessiontime}</code>
          <desc>
            The amount of time played this session, or since the last
            session reset.
          </desc>
          <type>Time</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{leveltime}</code>
          <desc>The amount of time played at this character level.</desc>
          <type>Time</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{sessionxprate}</code>
          <desc>The average rate of experience gain this session.</desc>
          <type>Number</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{levelxprate}</code>
          <desc>The average rate of experience gain this level.</desc>
          <type>Number</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{income}</code>
          <desc>The amount of money earned this session.</desc>
          <type>Money</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{expense}</code>
          <desc>The amount of money earned this session.</desc>
          <type>Money</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{netincome}</code>
          <desc>
            The net amount of money earned (or lost) this session.  
            This is the same as {income} - {expense}.
          </desc>
          <type>Money</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{incomerate}</code>
          <desc>The average amount of money earned per hour this session.</desc>
          <type>Money</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{expenserate}</code>
          <desc>The average amount of money spent per hour this session.</desc>
          <type>Money</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{netincomerate}</code>
          <desc>
            The net amount of money earned (or lost) per hour this session.  
            This is the same as {incomerate} - {expenserate}.
          </desc>
          <type>Money</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{factionname}</code>
          <desc>
            The name of the indicated faction.  Since this returns the same
            thing as the faction name indicated, it is not expected to be
            very useful.
          </desc>
          <type>Faction</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{factionstanding}</code>
          <desc>
            Your current standing with the indicated faction: Friendly,
            Hostile, etc.
          </desc>
          <type>Faction</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{reputation}</code>
          <desc>
            Your current reputation with the indicated faction, expressed
            as a number.  This is the same number that shows up on your
            character's reputation panel.
          </desc>
          <type>Faction</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{reputationmax}</code>
          <desc>
            The maximum number of reputation points you can earn with the
            indicated faction, before advancing to the next standing.
          </desc>
          <type>Faction</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{reputation%}</code>
          <desc>
            Your current reputation with the indicated faction, expressed
            as a percentage of the maximum points in this standing.
          </desc>
          <type>Faction, Number</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{factionatwar}</code>
          <desc>
            Indicates whether or not you are at war with the indicated
            faction.
          </desc>
          <type>Faction, Boolean</type>
        </var>
      </variable-list>
    </subsection>
    <subsection name="Variables provided by NoxCombatStats">
      <variable-list>
        <var>
          <code>{dps}</code>
          <desc>Damage per second this fight.</desc>
          <type>Number</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{hps}</code>
          <desc>Healing per second this fight.</desc>
          <type>Number</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{petdps}</code>
          <desc>Pet damage per second fight.</desc>
          <type>Number</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{totaldamage}</code>
          <desc>Total damage dealt this fight.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{totalheal}</code>
          <desc>Total points healed this fight.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{combatduration}</code>
          <desc>Time spent in combat this fight.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{meleehits}</code>
          <desc>Number of melee hits this fight.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{meleemisses}</code>
          <desc>Number of melee misses this fight.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{meleecrits}</code>
          <desc>Number of melee critical hits this fight.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{meleehits%}</code>
          <desc>Percentage of melee hits this fight.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{meleemisses%}</code>
          <desc>Percentage of melee misses this fight.</desc>
          <type>Number</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{meleecrits%}</code>
          <desc>Percentage of melee critical hits this fight.</desc>
          <type>Number</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{nonmeleehits}</code>
          <desc>Number of non-melee hits this fight.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{nonmeleemisses}</code>
          <desc>Number of non-melee misses this fight.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{nonmeleecrits}</code>
          <desc>Number of non-melee critical hits this fight.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{nonmeleehits%}</code>
          <desc>Percentage of non-melee hits this fight.</desc>
          <type>Number</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{nonmeleemisses%}</code>
          <desc>Percentage of non-melee misses this fight.</desc>
          <type>Number</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{nonmeleecrits%}</code>
          <desc>Percentage of non-melee critical hits this fight.</desc>
          <type>Number</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{healhits}</code>
          <desc>Number of successful heals this fight.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{healmisses}</code>
          <desc>Number of failed heals this fight.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{healcrits}</code>
          <desc>Number of critical heals this fight.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{healhits%}</code>
          <desc>Percentage of successful heals this fight.</desc>
          <type>Number</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{healmisses%}</code>
          <desc>Percentage of failed heals this fight.</desc>
          <type>Number</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{healcrits%}</code>
          <desc>Percentage of critical heals this fight.</desc>
          <type>Number</type>
        </var>


        <var>
          <code>{sessiondps}</code>
          <desc>Damage per second, averaged over this session.</desc>
          <type>Number</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{sessionhps}</code>
          <desc>Healing per second, averaged over this session.</desc>
          <type>Number</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{sessionpetdps}</code>
          <desc>Pet damage per second, averaged over this session.</desc>
          <type>Number</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{sessiontotaldamage}</code>
          <desc>Total damage dealt this session.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{sessiontotalheal}</code>
          <desc>Total points healed this session.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{sessioncombatduration}</code>
          <desc>Time spent in combat this session.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{sessionmeleehits}</code>
          <desc>Number of melee hits this session.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{sessionmeleemisses}</code>
          <desc>Number of melee misses this session.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{sessionmeleecrits}</code>
          <desc>Number of melee critical hits this session.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{sessionmeleehits%}</code>
          <desc>Percentage of melee hits this session.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{sessionmeleemisses%}</code>
          <desc>Percentage of melee misses this session.</desc>
          <type>Number</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{sessionmeleecrits%}</code>
          <desc>Percentage of melee critical hits this session.</desc>
          <type>Number</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{sessionnonmeleehits}</code>
          <desc>Number of non-melee hits this session.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{sessionnonmeleemisses}</code>
          <desc>Number of non-melee misses this session.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{sessionnonmeleecrits}</code>
          <desc>Number of non-melee critical hits this session.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{sessionnonmeleehits%}</code>
          <desc>Percentage of non-melee hits this session.</desc>
          <type>Number</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{sessionnonmeleemisses%}</code>
          <desc>Percentage of non-melee misses this session.</desc>
          <type>Number</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{sessionnonmeleecrits%}</code>
          <desc>Percentage of non-melee critical hits this session.</desc>
          <type>Number</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{sessionhealhits}</code>
          <desc>Number of successful heals this session.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{sessionhealmisses}</code>
          <desc>Number of failed heals this session.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{sessionhealcrits}</code>
          <desc>Number of critical heals this session.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{sessionhealhits%}</code>
          <desc>Percentage of successful heals this session.</desc>
          <type>Number</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{sessionhealmisses%}</code>
          <desc>Percentage of failed heals this session.</desc>
          <type>Number</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{sessionhealcrits%}</code>
          <desc>Percentage of critical heals this session.</desc>
          <type>Number</type>
        </var>

        <var>
          <code>{kills}</code>
          <desc>
            The number of kills made by your party this session.
          </desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{xpperkill}</code>
          <desc>
            The average experienced gained per kill for your last four
            kills.
          </desc>
          <type>Number</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{killstolevel}</code>
          <desc>
            The estimated number of kills needed to gain the next
            character level, based on the average experience gained
            from your last four kills.
          </desc>
          <type>Number</type>
        </var>
      </variable-list>
    </subsection>
    <subsection name="Variables provided by NoxEquipmentStats">
      <variable-list>
        <var>
          <code>{equipslot}</code>
          <desc>
            The name of the slot where the item is equipped (eg. "Head", 
            "Legs", etc).
          </desc>
          <type>Equipment</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{equipname}</code>
          <desc>The name of the item equipped in the named slot.</desc>
          <type>Equipment</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{currdurability}</code>
          <desc>The current durability of the item in the named slot.</desc>
          <type>Equipment</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{maxdurability}</code>
          <desc>The maximum durability of the item in the named slot.</desc>
          <type>Equipment</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{durability%}</code>
          <desc>
            The percent durability of the item in the named slot.  An
            item at 100% is in perfect condition, and one at 0% is broken.
          </desc>
          <type>Equipment</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{repaircost}</code>
          <desc>
            The amount of money required to repair the item in the named slot.
          </desc>
          <type>Equipment, Money</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{totalrepaircost}</code>
          <desc>
            The amount of money required to repair all equipped items.  This
            does not count damaged items in your bags.
          </desc>
          <type>Money</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{totalcurrdurability}</code>
          <desc>
            The total current durability of all of your equipped items.  This
            gives you a general feel for your overall equipment damage.
          </desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{totalmaxdurability}</code>
          <desc>
            The total maximum durability of all of your equipped items.
          </desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{totaldurability%}</code>
          <desc>
            The percent durability of all of your equipped items.  At 100%,
            all of your equipment is in perfect condition.  At 0%, it is
            all broken.  Note that you may have some broken items and still
            have more than 0% total durability.
          </desc>
          <type>Number</type>
        </var>
      </variable-list>
    </subsection>
    <subsection name="Variables provided by NoxHonorStats">
      <variable-list>
        <var>
          <code>{lifetimehk}</code>
          <desc>Number of honorable kills over lifetime.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{lifetimerank}</code>
          <desc>Highest rank achieved over lifetime.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{yesterdayhk}</code>
          <desc>Number of honorable kills earned yesterday.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{yesterdayhonor}</code>
          <desc>Number of honor points earned yesterday.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{todayhk}</code>
          <desc>Number of honorable kills earned today.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{todayhonor}</code>
          <desc>Number of honor points earned today.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{currentrank}</code>
          <desc>Player's current rank.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{currentstanding}</code>
          <desc>Player's current numeric standing.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{rankprogress}</code>
          <desc>Player's percentage progress towards next PvP rank.</desc>
          <type>Number</type>
        </var>
      </variable-list>
    </subsection>
    <subsection name="Variables provided by NoxPlayerStats">
      <variable-list>
        <var>
          <code>{name}</code>
          <desc>Current character's name.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{class}</code>
          <desc>Current character's class.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{realm}</code>
          <desc>Current character's realm.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{sex}</code>
          <desc>Current character's sex.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{race}</code>
          <desc>Current character's race.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{faction}</code>
          <desc>Current character's faction (Horde or Alliance).</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{strength}</code>
          <desc>
            The character's current strength score, colored for bonuses and 
            penalties.
          </desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{agility}</code>
          <desc>
            The character's current agility score, colored for bonuses and
            penalties.
          </desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{stamina}</code>
          <desc>
            The character's current stamina score, colored for bonuses and
            penalties.
          </desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{intellect}</code>
          <desc>
            The character's current intellect score, colored for bonuses and
            penalties.
          </desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{spirit}</code>
          <desc>
            The character's current spirit score, colored for bonuses and
            penalties.
          </desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{armor}</code>
          <desc>
            The character's current armor score, colored for bonuses and
            penalties.
          </desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{resistholy}</code>
          <desc>The character's current holy magic resistance.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{resistarcane}</code>
          <desc>The character's current arcane magic resistance.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{resistfire}</code>
          <desc>The character's current fire magic resistance.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{resistnature}</code>
          <desc>The character's current nature magic resistance.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{resistfrost}</code>
          <desc>The character's current frost magic resistance.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{resistshadow}</code>
          <desc>The character's current shadow magic resistance.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{zone}</code>
          <desc>
            Current zone the character is in.  Colored green if the
            player is in friendly territory, red in hostile territory
            and arenas, orange in contested territory, and yellow
            everywhere else.
          </desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{subzone}</code>
          <desc>Current subzone the character is in.  Colored like {zone}.</desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{shortzone}</code>
          <desc>
            The zone name as it appears in the minimap.  Seems to be the 
            same thing as subzone.  Colored like {zone}
          </desc>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{realzone}</code>
          <desc>
            The real name of an instance if the player is in one, otherwise
            the same as {zone}.  Colored like {zone}.
          </desc>
        </var>
      </variable-list>
    </subsection>
    <subsection name="Variables provided by NoxSkillStats">
      <variable-list>
        <var>
          <code>{skillrank}</code>
          <desc>The character's current level in the named skill.</desc>
          <type>Skill</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{skillmax}</code>
          <desc>The character's maximum level in the named skill.</desc>
          <type>Skill</type>
        </var>
        <var>
          <code>{skillname}</code>
          <desc>
            The name of the named skill.  This is most useful when
            used with the "generic" skill names like "Professions 1".
            In that case it will return the real name of the skill,
            instead of the generic name.
          </desc>
          <type>Skill</type>
        </var>
      </variable-list>
    </subsection>
    <subsection name="Variables provided by NoxMoneyExtension">
      <p>
        NoxMoneyExtension provides only one variable: {coins}.  This
        variable shows your current amount of money using coin
        graphics similar to what appears at the bottom of the
        backpack.  This variable can only be used in one slot at a
        time on the main bar, and must be the only thing in that slot.
        Currently the other money-related variables ({income},
        {repaircost}, etc.)  cannot be shown with coin graphics.
      </p>
    </subsection>
    <subsection name="Deprecated Variables">
      <p>
        This section lists variables that are being phased out and may
        disappear from future versions, but are still supported for backward
        compatibility.  All of these variables have newer equivalents using
        format codes, as shown in the table below.
      </p>
      <deprecated-variables>
        <depvar>
          <code>{sessionttlshort}</code>
          <desc>
            Estimated time to level for this session, in "d.h:m:s" format.
          </desc>
          <repl>{sessionttl:short}</repl>
        </depvar>
        <depvar>
          <code>{levelttlshort}</code>
          <desc>
            Estimated time to level for this level, in "d.h:m:s" format.
          </desc>
          <repl>{levelttl:short}</repl>
        </depvar>
        <depvar>
          <code>{bestttlshort}</code>
          <desc>
            Smallest of session TTL and level TTL, in "d.h:m:s" format.
          </desc>
          <repl>{bestttl:short}</repl>
        </depvar>
        <depvar>
          <code>{memmb}</code>
          <desc>UI memory used in megabytes.</desc>
          <repl>{mem:mb,int}</repl>
        </depvar>
        <depvar>
          <code>{memkb}</code>
          <desc>UI memory used in kilobytes.</desc>
          <repl>{mem:kb}</repl>
        </depvar>
        <depvar>
          <code>{memlimitmb}</code>
          <desc>UI memory GC threshold, in megabytes.</desc>
          <repl>{memlimit:mb,int}</repl>
        </depvar>
        <depvar>
          <code>{memlimitkb}</code>
          <desc>UI memory GC threshold, in kilobytes.</desc>
          <repl>{memlimit:kb}</repl>
        </depvar>
        <depvar>
          <code>{allmoney}</code>
          <desc>Money displayed in "0g 0s 0c" format.</desc>
          <repl>{money:short}</repl>
        </depvar>
        <depvar>
          <code>{gold}</code>
          <desc>Current amount of gold.</desc>
          <repl>{money:gold}</repl>
        </depvar>
        <depvar>
          <code>{silver}</code>
          <desc>Current amount of silver.</desc>
          <repl>{money:silver}</repl>
        </depvar>
        <depvar>
          <code>{copper}</code>
          <desc>Current amount of copper.</desc>
          <repl>{money:copper}</repl>
        </depvar>
        <depvar>
          <code>{yesterdaycp}</code>
          <desc>Number of contribution points earned yesterday.</desc>
          <repl>{yesterdayhonor}</repl>
        </depvar>
        <depvar>
          <code>{sessionhk}</code>
          <desc>Number of honorable kills earned this session.</desc>
          <repl>{todayhk}</repl>
        </depvar>
      </deprecated-variables>
    </subsection>
  </section>
  <section name="Supported Formats">
    <p>
      Formats are a new feature in version 2.0 that let you change the
      way many of the variables display their values.  This one
      feature adds a whole new layer of configurability to the Nox bar
      - as well as allowing for whole new types of variables.  The
      sections shown here match up with the allowed formats shown in
      the tables of variables above.
    </p>
    <p>
      To use a format, you simply place a colon after the variable name,
      <i>inside</i> the brackets, and place one of the format names shown
      below after it.  There should be no spaces between the colon and
      the format name, or between the format name and the end brace.  Some
      formats allow multiple options at once, and in this case you simply
      separate each option with a comma, again with no extra spaces.  Multiple
      options <i>must</i> be specified in the order shown below.
    </p>
    <p>
      Except where noted, formats are always optional - if you leave them
      out, the variable will display itself using a reasonable default format.
    </p>
    <p>
      For example, to display the total time played in a shortened form,
      you would use:
    </p>
    <block>
      {totaltime:short}
    </block>
    <p>
      To display your current money in a long form, with the numbers and
      letters colored like coins, you would use:
    </p>
    <block>
      {money:long,1,1}
    </block>
    <p>
      To display the total time played in the default format, which happens
      to be the same as the medium format, you would use:
    </p>
    <block>
      {totaltime}
    </block>
    <p>
      Note in this case that since the formats are left out, the colon is
      left out too.
    </p>
    <subsection name="Number Formats">
      <p>
        Numbers can be displayed as integers, or as real numbers with
        two decimal places.
      </p>
      <format-list>
        <format>
          <spec>int</spec>
          <desc>
            Displays the value as an integer.  Any fractional part is
            truncated.
          </desc>
          <example>
            10
          </example>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>dec</spec>
          <desc>
            Displays the value as a real number with two decimal places.
          </desc>
          <example>
            21.34
          </example>
        </format>
      </format-list>
    </subsection>
    <subsection name="Boolean Formats">
      <p>
        Boolean variables express a value that can be <i>true</i> or
        <i>false</i>.  Normally these variables will print either the name
        "true" or the name "false", depending on their value.  Boolean
        formats let you change either or both of these names.
      </p>
      <p>
        Boolean formats are expressed as {<i>variable</i>:<i>text if true</i>,<i>text if false</i>}.  Either of the text values may be omitted, but note that if you include a false value without a true value, you must still include the comma.
      </p>
      <p>
        For example, to print "yes" or "no" instead of "true" and "false", you
        would use:
      </p>
      <block>
        {factionatwar:Bloodsail Buccaneers,yes,no}
      </block>
      <p>
        (The "Bloodsail Buccaneers" part is the required "faction" format
        for this variable, explained below, and is not part of the boolean
        format.  The boolean part follows it.)
      </p>
      <p>
        If instead you wanted the text "At War" to show up in red only when
        you were at war, you would use:
      </p>
      <block>
        {factionatwar:Everlook,|cffff0000At War}
      </block>
      <p>
        By contrast, this is how you would do it if you only wanted "At Peace"
        to show up in green:
      </p>
      <block>
        {factionatwar:Everlook,,|cff00ff00At Peace}
      </block>
      <p>
        Note the extra comma in the format, reserving the "empty" true value.
      </p>
      <p>
        See below for a discussion of color codes.
      </p>
    </subsection>
    <subsection name="Time Formats">
      <p>
        Times can be displayed in forms of different lengths.
      </p>
      <format-list>
        <format>
          <spec>long</spec>
          <desc>
            Displays the time with each increment spelled out in full.
          </desc>
          <example>
            1 day, 21 hours, 36 minutes, 5 seconds
          </example>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>medium</spec>
          <desc>
            Displays the time with abbreviations for each increment.
          </desc>
          <example>
            1d 21h 36m 5s
          </example>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>short</spec>
          <desc>
            Displays the time in a compacted format, without increment names.
          </desc>
          <example>
            1.21:36:05
          </example>
        </format>
      </format-list>
    </subsection>
    <subsection name="Money Formats">
      <p>
        Money can be displayed in a great variety of formats affecting not
        only how it is shown, but even <i>what part</i> is shown.  Money
        values can even be colored like the coins - yellow for gold, grey
        for silver, and orange for copper.  To color the coins, just include
        a ",1" at the end of the format, or ",1,1" to color the number and
        the name of the coin, for formats that include names.
      </p>
      <p>
        Money formats can even be used to extract part of a money
        value.  For instance, if you are only interested in the amount
        of gold you have, you can use the "gold" format to show only
        that part.  The "as gold" format will show you the same thing,
        but will also include your silver as a decimal fraction.  Note
        that this behavior is not exactly the same for silver and
        copper formats.  For example "silver" will show you
        <i>only</i> the silver part, but "as silver" will also include
        gold in the value as 100's of silver.
      </p>
      <p>
        This means that a slot configured like:
      </p>
      <block>
        {money:gold}g {money:silver}s {money:copper}c
      </block>
      <p>
        will display the same thing as:
      </p>
      <block>
        {money:short}
      </block>
      <p>
        Note that the latter takes less processing power from the
        game, though.  (Actually these examples are not strictly the
        same - the "short" format will omit the gold portion if it is
        zero, and the silver portion if both gold and silver are zero.
        The version with three variables will always show all
        portions, even if they are zero.)
      </p>
      <p>
        Money variables support the following formats:
      </p>
      <format-list>
        <format>
          <spec>as gold[,dec[,1]]</spec>
          <desc>
            Display the total amount as gold, with silver after the
            decimal.  The number format "dec" may optionally be
            included, but <i>must</i> be included if you want to color
            the number gold (with ",1").
          </desc>
          <example>
            1.02
          </example>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>as gold,int[,1]</spec>
          <desc>
            Display the total amount in gold, as a whole number.  The
            "int" portion is the number format for whole numbers.
            Include the ",1" to color the number gold.
          </desc>
          <example>
            1
          </example>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>as silver[,dec[,1]]</spec>
          <desc>
            Display the total amount as silver, with copper after the
            decimal.  The number format "dec" may optionally be
            included, but <i>must</i> be included if you want to color
            the number silver (with ",1").
          </desc>
          <example>
            102.03
          </example>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>as silver,int[,1]</spec>
          <desc>
            Display the total amount in silver, as a whole number.
            The "int" portion is the number format for whole numbers.
            Include the ",1" to color the number silver.
          </desc>
          <example>
            102
          </example>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>as copper,dec[,1]</spec>
          <desc>
            Display the total amount as copper, with zeros after the
            decimal.  The "dec" portion is the number format for real
            numbers.  Include the ",1" to color the number copper.
          </desc>
          <example>
            10203.00
          </example>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>as copper[,int[,1]]</spec>
          <desc>
            Display the total amount in copper, as a whole number.
            The number format "int" may optionally be included, but
            <i>must</i> be included if you want to color the number
            copper (with ",1").
          </desc>
          <example>
            10203
          </example>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>gold[,1]</spec>
          <desc>
            Display the gold portion of the amount.  Include the ",1"
            to color the number gold.
          </desc>
          <example>
            1
          </example>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>silver[,1]</spec>
          <desc>
            Display the silver portion of the amount.  Include the
            ",1" to color the number silver.
          </desc>
          <example>
            2
          </example>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>copper[,1]</spec>
          <desc>
            Display the copper portion of the amount.  Include the
            ",1" to color the number copper.
          </desc>
          <example>
            3
          </example>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>long[,1[,1]]</spec>
          <desc>
            Display the total amount spelled out.  If gold is zero, it will be
            omitted.  If both gold and silver are zero, both will be omitted.
            Copper is always shown.  Include ",1" to color the
            numbers only, or ",1,1" to color the numbers and words.
          </desc>
          <example>
            1 gold 2 silver 3 copper
          </example>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>short[,1[,1]]</spec>
          <desc>
            Display the total amount with abbreviations.  If gold is zero, 
            it will be omitted.  If both gold and silver are zero, both will 
            be omitted. Copper is always shown.  Include ",1" to color the
            numbers only, or ",1,1" to color the numbers and words.
          </desc>
          <example>
            1g 2s 3c
          </example>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>numeric[,1]</spec>
          <desc>
            Display the total amount in numbers only.  If gold is zero, 
            it will be omitted.  If both gold and silver are zero, both will 
            be omitted. Copper is always shown.  Include ",1" to color the
            numbers.
          </desc>
          <example>
            1 2 3
          </example>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>compact[,1]</spec>
          <desc>
            Display the total amount in numbers only, with separators between
            each number.  If gold is zero, it will be omitted.  If both gold 
            and silver are zero, both will be omitted. Copper is always shown.
            Include ",1" to color the numbers.
          </desc>
          <example>
            1.2.3
          </example>
        </format>
      </format-list>
    </subsection>
    <subsection name="Memory Formats">
      <p>
        Memory formats allow you to display memory values as kilobytes or
        megabytes.
      </p>
      <format-list>
        <format>
          <spec>kb</spec>
          <desc>
            Display the amount in kilobytes.
          </desc>
          <example>
            21345
          </example>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>mb[,dec]</spec>
          <desc>
            Display the amount in megabytes, to two decimal places.
          </desc>
          <example>
            21.34
          </example>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>mb,int</spec>
          <desc>
            Display the amount in megabytes, truncated to the nearest whole 
            megabyte.
          </desc>
          <example>
            21
          </example>
        </format>
      </format-list>
    </subsection>
    <subsection name="Equipment Formats">
      <p>
        Equipment "formats" don't actually affect <i>how</i> a variable
        is displayed, rather, they determine which equipment slot the
        variable reports about.  The equipment format is required for
        variables that use it.  If it is omitted or unknown, the variable
        that uses it will display "n/a" instead.
      </p>
      <p>
        The names below can be used for equipment formats.  Note that
        several alias names are included for convenience, but all names
        work the same way.  For example, both "shoulders" and "pauldrons"
        can be used to refer to the shoulder item, regardless of what is
        worn there.  These are used just like normal format codes.  For 
        example, {repaircost:chest} will display the repair cost of the
        armor worn on your character's chest, and {equipname:trinket1}
        will return the name of your first equipped trinket. 
      </p>
      <equip-list>
        <format>
          <spec>head</spec>
          <desc>Head</desc>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>helm</spec>
          <desc>Head</desc>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>hat</spec>
          <desc>Head</desc>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>goggles</spec>
          <desc>Head</desc>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>shoulders</spec>
          <desc>Shoulders</desc>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>pauldrons</spec>
          <desc>Shoulders</desc>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>chest</spec>
          <desc>Chest</desc>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>torso</spec>
          <desc>Chest</desc>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>robe</spec>
          <desc>Chest</desc>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>vest</spec>
          <desc>Chest</desc>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>breastplate</spec>
          <desc>Chest</desc>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>tunic</spec>
          <desc>Chest</desc>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>wrist</spec>
          <desc>Wrists</desc>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>bracers</spec>
          <desc>Wrists</desc>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>hands</spec>
          <desc>Hands</desc>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>gloves</spec>
          <desc>Hands</desc>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>gauntlets</spec>
          <desc>Hands</desc>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>waist</spec>
          <desc>Waist</desc>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>belt</spec>
          <desc>Waist</desc>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>legs</spec>
          <desc>Legs</desc>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>pants</spec>
          <desc>Legs</desc>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>skirt</spec>
          <desc>Legs</desc>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>kilt</spec>
          <desc>Legs</desc>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>leggings</spec>
          <desc>Legs</desc>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>feet</spec>
          <desc>Feet</desc>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>boots</spec>
          <desc>Feet</desc>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>shoes</spec>
          <desc>Feet</desc>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>mainhand</spec>
          <desc>Main Hand Weapon</desc>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>weapon</spec>
          <desc>Main Hand Weapon</desc>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>offhand</spec>
          <desc>Off-hand Weapon</desc>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>shield</spec>
          <desc>Off-hand Weapon</desc>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>ranged</spec>
          <desc>Ranged Weapon</desc>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>gun</spec>
          <desc>Ranged Weapon</desc>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>bow</spec>
          <desc>Ranged Weapon</desc>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>finger1</spec>
          <desc>Finger</desc>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>ring1</spec>
          <desc>Finger</desc>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>finger2</spec>
          <desc>Finger</desc>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>ring2</spec>
          <desc>Finger</desc>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>trinket1</spec>
          <desc>Trinket</desc>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>trinket2</spec>
          <desc>Trinket</desc>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>neck</spec>
          <desc>Neck</desc>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>necklace</spec>
          <desc>Neck</desc>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>pendant</spec>
          <desc>Neck</desc>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>back</spec>
          <desc>Back</desc>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>cloak</spec>
          <desc>Back</desc>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>shirt</spec>
          <desc>Shirt</desc>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>tabard</spec>
          <desc>Tabard</desc>
        </format>
        <format>
          <spec>ammo</spec>
          <desc>Ammo</desc>
        </format>
      </equip-list>
    </subsection>
    <subsection name="Skills Formats">
      <p>
        Skills "formats" determine which skill a variable applies to, rather
        than changing the look of the variable.  Because of this, skills
        formats are required for those variables that use them.  If the skill
        format is omitted, misspelled, or if your character does not know
        the skill named, skills variables will display "n/a" instead.
      </p>
      <p>
        Normally, skill formats are entered exactly as the names read on
        your character's skill panel, for example "Leatherworking" or
        "Daggers".  So, for instance, if you wanted to know your current
        alchemy skill, you could use the variable "{skillrank:Alchemy}". 
        Note the capitalization of the name - it must appear <i>exactly</i>
        as it does on the skills panel.
      </p>
      <p>
        Skills variables also support "generic" skill formats.  These are
        special names you can use to refer to your skill when you don't
        know ahead of time what the real skill name is.  The generic
        names are formed by taking the name of the skill group on the
        skills panel (for example, "Professions") and adding a number to
        the end of it which corresponds to the number of the skill in the
        group.  So, for example, "Professions 1" refers to your first
        profession skill, and "Weapon Skills 5" refers to your fifth weapon
        skill, as shown on the skills panel.
      </p>
      <p>
        The generic names for professions ("Professions 1" and
        "Professions 2") are the most useful, as they let you set up
        displays that work for all of your characters, regardless of
        what professions they have.  If you use these, you might also
        find the {skillname} variable useful for returning the real
        name of the skill.  For instance, the variable
        {skillname:Professions 1} will display the real name of your
        first profession, no matter what it is.
      </p>
    </subsection>
    <subsection name="Faction Formats">
      <p>
        Like skill formats, faction "formats" determine which faction
        a variable applies to, rather than changing the look of the
        variable.  Because of this, faction formats are required for
        those variables that use them.  If the faction format is
        omitted, misspelled, or if your character has no reputation with
        the named faction, faction variables will display "n/a" instead.
      </p>
      <p>
        Faction formats are entered exactly as the names read on
        your character's reputation panel, for example "Ironforge" or
        "Cenarion Circle".  So, for instance, if you wanted to know your 
        current reputation with Honor Hold, you would use the variable 
        "{reputation:Honor Hold}".
        Note the capitalization of the name - it must appear <i>exactly</i>
        as it does on the reputation panel.
      </p>
    </subsection>
    <subsection name="Color Codes">
      <p>
        Any slot can be colored by entering the following code before it:
      </p>
      <block>
        |c<i>aarrggbb</i>
      </block>
      <p>
        where
      </p>
      <block>
        <i>aa</i> is the alpha (transparency) value,
      </block>
      <block>
        <i>rr</i> is the red value,
      </block>
      <block>
        <i>gg</i> is the green value, and
      </block>
      <block>
        <i>bb</i> is the blue value.
      </block>
      <p>
        All color values are given as two hexadecimal digits from "00"
        (no color, or transparent in the case of the alpha value) to "ff" 
        (full color, or opaque for the alpha value).
      </p>
      <p>
        Also, the code:
      </p>
      <block>
        |r
      </block>
      <p>
        will restore the color that was in effect before the last
        color change.  Even if you leave off the restore code, your
        color changes will only affect the slot they appear in -
        colors will not bleed into adjacent slots.  This also means
        that every slot must be colored independently.  Also, each
        slot can have several color codes, and the restore code is not
        required between each color change.
      </p>
      <p>
        For example, a slot containing the display string
        '|cffff0000{dps}|r dps' will display the current dps in opaque
        red (ff, ff, 00, 00), and then " dps" in the default color
        (which is a nearly pure yellow).  As another example, the
        display string '|cffff0000r|cff00ff00g|cff0000ffb' will
        display a red 'r', a green 'g', and a blue 'b'.
      </p>
      <p>
        Note that color codes will have no effect when used with
        variables that color themselves, such as {latency}.
      </p>
    </subsection>
  </section>
  <section name="More Information">
    <p>
      For more information, or to download the latest version of Nox
      Information Bar, see the addon page on Curse Gaming at
      <a href="http://wow.curse-gaming.com/downloads/details/1008/">http://wow.curse-gaming.com/downloads/details/1008/</a>.
    </p>
  </section>
</user-guide>