<changelog>
  <project>Nox Information Bar</project>
  <topic>Version History</topic>
  <version number="3.0.0" author="Gruma" date="2008/11/22">
    <change>
      Raised the level limit to 80.
    </change>
    <change>
      Fixed the combat stats to work with 3.0.
    </change>
    <change>
      The honor stats weren't actually broken, so they're fixed too.
    </change>
    <change>
      Fixed the money extension to work with 3.0.
    </change>
    <change>
      Changed the way the money extension works to make it possible to have multiple coin displays in the future.
    </change>
  </version>
  <version number="3.0.0pre" author="Gruma" date="2008/11/15">
    <change>
      Updated the TOC for 3.0.
    </change>
    <change>
      Removed the {memlimit} variable.  This value is no longer available from the WoW client.
    </change>
    <change>
      Fixed the basics that were broken by the 3.0 update.
    </change>
  </version>
  <version number="2.6" author="Gruma" date="2007/06/03">
    <change>
      Added font scaling for the main bar.
    </change>
    <change>
      Added new faction/reputation variables.  The new variables include:
      <ul>
        <li>{faction name:}</li>
        <li>{faction standing:}</li>
        <li>{reputation:}</li>
        <li>{reputation max:}</li>
        <li>{reputation %:}</li>
        <li>{faction at war:}</li>
      </ul>
    </change>
    <change>
      Updated myAddons support.
    </change>
    <change>
      Updated latency colors to match Blizzard's interpretation (I think).
    </change>
  </version>
  <version number="2.5.2" author="Gruma" date="2007/05/25">
    <change>
      Updated to work with WoW 2.1.
    </change>
    <change>
      Fixed the player coordinates so that they track across zone
      changes correctly.
    </change>
    <change>
      Fixed column titles on the slot configuration GUI to display
      properly.
    </change>
  </version>
  <version number="2.5.1" author="Gruma" date="2007/02/04">
    <change>
      Updated to work with Burning Crusade (raised the level limit).
    </change>
  </version>
  <version number="2.5" author="Gruma" date="2006/12/12">
    <change>
      Updated to work with WoW 2.0.
    </change>
  </version>
  <version number="2.4.1" author="Gruma" date="2006/04/07">
    <change>
      Fixed bugs that caused the tooltips and the buff icon mover
      to get reset to defaults at login.
    </change>
  </version>
  <version number="2.4" author="Gruma" date="2006/04/03">
    <change>
      Fixed a startup bug for new users.  Thanks to DrWiggly for
      spotting this one and tracking it down.
    </change>
    <change>
      Fixed equipment stats for client version 1.10.
    </change>
    <change>
      Removed the default coloring for the {mem} variable, since
      the upper limit is (and has been for a while) configurable now.
    </change>
    <change>
      Updated to client version 1.10.
    </change>
  </version>
  <version number="2.3" author="Gruma" date="2006/01/03">
    <change>
      Added per-character configuration options.  Switches now appear
      in the config GUI that allow specific groups of options to be
      overridden for each character.  This required a fairly extensive
      rework of the configuration code, so bugs are expected.
    </change>
    <change>
      Fixed a problem that caused an occasional error message in
      NoxSkillStats when zoning in.
    </change>
    <change>
      Changed tab selection buttons in the config GUI to real tabs.
    </change>
  </version>
  <version number="2.2" author="Gruma" date="2005/09/06">
    <change>
      Reduced the number of tooltip lines to 30.  This seems to be all
      the game will support in the default tooltip.
    </change>
    <change>
      Enabled the shift-tab key in the tooltip edit dialog. (finally)
    </change>
    <change>
      Added buttons to insert and delete lines in the tooltip edit
      dialog.
    </change>
    <change>
      Changed the display for unknown skills from "n/a" to "0".
    </change>
    <change>
      Added per-session combat stats.  In general, just add "session"
      in front of any existing combat stat to get the session
      cumulative version.  (For example, {crit%} becomes {session
      crit%}.)  See the docs for complete details.
    </change>
    <change>
      Added a menu option to reset session combat stats independently
      of other session variables.
    </change>
    <change>
      Added new variables for {kills}, {xp per kill} and {kills to
      level} to Nox Combat Stats.  {xp per kill} and {kills to level}
      are both averages based on the last four kills made.  Note that
      kills that don't net you experience ("grey" kills) are not
      counted in any of these variables, since the game doesn't
      provide any way to distinguish your non-xp kills from the kills
      of other nearby players.  (Yes, your chat log even shows kills
      from nearby players who aren't in your party!)
    </change>
  </version>
  <version number="2.1.1" author="Gruma" date="2005/08/19">
    <change>
      Fixed the {healcrits%}, {healmisses}, {healmisses%},
      {nonmeleecrits%}, {nonmeleemisses}, and {nonmeleemisses%}
      variables in NoxCombatStats.  Note that heal misses and
      non-melee misses don't actually happen, but there are variables
      for them anyway.
    </change>
    <change>
      Added coloring to zone text in NoxPlayerStats.  Zone names will
      now be colored just like the minimap text - green for friendly
      territory, red for hostile territory, and orange for contested
      territories and yellow for everything else.  This applies to the
      {zone}, {shortzone}, {subzone}, and {realzone} variables.
    </change>
    <change>
      Added the {realzone} variable to NoxPlayerStats.  This variable
      displays the real name of the instance if the player is in one, 
      otherwise it displays the same thing as {zone}.
    </change>
  </version>
  <version number="2.1" author="Gruma" date="2005/07/12">
    <change>
      Slightly changed the way durability is recognized to hopefully
      eliminate random errors with the German client.
    </change>
    <change>
      Made the border and background of the bar hideable.
    </change>
    <change>
      Added the {totalcurrdurability}, {totalmaxdurability}, and 
      {totaldurability%} variables to NoxEquipment stats.
    </change>
    <change>
      Changed to allow optional spaces in variable names, so for example
      you could use {total curr durability} instead of {totalcurrdurability}.
    </change>
    <change>
      Changed to allow optional uppercase in variables names, so for
      example you could use {TotalCurrDurability} instead of
      {totalcurrdurability}.  You can even combine this with the
      optional spaces enhancement and use {Total Curr Durability}.
      Note that using spaces or uppercase may increase your dynamic
      memory usage rate slightly.  (If you don't understand what that
      means, don't worry about it.)
    </change>
    <change>
      Updated for client version 1.6 (interface version 1600).
    </change>
    <change>
      Added new variables for today's and this week's honor points, and
      for rank progress.  See the user's guide for details.  Please note
      that I am guessing how rank progress works at the moment, and that
      DK stats for yesterday and last week might not work correctly anymore.
      The DK stats are still in the API, but the default UI no longer uses
      them.  If you discover any problems with either the progress or DK
      stats, please let me know.
    </change>
    <change>
      Changed honor "cp" variables to "honor" variables.  This should have
      been done after the last patch when Blizzard changed the names in the
      default UI.  Oops.
    </change>
    <change>
      Fixed an occasional bug in NoxEquipmentStats referring to a nil
      repairCost value.
    </change>
  </version>
  <version number="2.0.1" date="2005/06/28" author="Gruma">
    <change>
      Improved the new variable rendering to correctly handle
      nested (decorative) braces.
    </change>
  </version>
  <version number="2.0" date="2005/06/26" author="Gruma">
    <change>
      Reworked the rendering core to allow options for variables.
      This adds a huge amount of configurability.
    </change>
    <change>
      Made the tooltip configurable using the same variables as
      the bar itself.  Unfortunately this means that tooltip lines
      will no longer hide themselves for level 60 chars.
    </change>
    <change>
      Revised the time to level estimates so that they return "n/a"
      for level 60 chars.
    </change>
    <change>
      Added many variables, added options to many others, and deprecated
      a few that are now redundant.  See the documentation for specifics.
    </change>
    <change>
      Expanded the number of available slots to 16.
    </change>
    <change>
      Combined the NoxMoveBuffs and NoxMoveBGFlag extensions into a single
      NoxMover extension.
    </change>
    <change>
      Added the ability to move the minimap, target frame, and player
      frame to the NoxMover.
    </change>
    <change>
      Moved the variables handled by NoxSampleExtension into a new "real"
      extension - NoxPlayerStats.  NoxSampleExtension now handles only
      junk variables.
    </change>
    <change>
      Added the NoxEquipmentStats extension to add inventory and
      durability variables to the bar.
    </change>
    <change>
      Added the NoxSkillStats extension to add skills variables to the
      bar.
    </change>
    <change>
      Rewrote the documentation.  It should be much more complete now.
    </change>
    <change>
      Revised the config GUI to handle the additional slots, tooltip 
      configuration, and mover configuration.
    </change>
  </version>
  <version number="1.8.4" date="2005/06/13" author="Gruma">
    <change>
     Fixed NoxMoveBuffs so that it will correctly use the offsets
     configured in SavedVariables.
    </change>
    <change>
      Added NoxMoveBGFlag to move the "capture the flag" icon down a
      few pixels.
    </change>
  </version>
  <version number="1.8.3" date="2005/06/10" author="Gruma">
    <change>
      Added a missing "round" function to fix problems with NoxMoveBuffs
      and two of the memory variables.
    </change>
    <change>
      Improved the way "time played" messages are blocked from showing in
      chat.
    </change>
    <change>
      Made NoxMoveBuffs save its offsets, for primitive configurability.
    </change>
  </version>
  <version number="1.8.2" date="2005/06/07" author="Gruma">
    <change>Updated for interface version 1500 (client patch 1.5.0).</change>
  </version>
  <version number="1.8.1" date="2005/06/06" author="Gruma">
    <change>Corrected a minor issue with the German translation that prevented the tooltip from working with that client.</change>
  </version>
  <version number="1.4" date="2005/04/01" author="ins0mniaque">
    <change>Added German translation provided by Wolfgang St&#x00f6;ckle. Danke sch&#x00f6;n!</change>
    <change>Changed TOC to 1300.</change>
  </version>
  <version number="1.8" date="2005/06/04" author="Gruma">
    <change>
      Added a configuration GUI.  This can be invoked by the right-clicking
      this bar, through myAddOns, or by the command "/noxib config".
    </change>
    <change>
      Removed the slash command for colors, as this was never implemented.
      Colors can be configured through the new GUI.
    </change>
    <change>
      Added usage summaries for all slash commands.
    </change>
    <change>
      Added compatibility with MyAddOns.
    </change>
    <change>
      Moved combat stats to a separate bundled addon, NoxCombatStats.
    </change>
    <change>
      Added honor stats via a separate bundled addon, NoxHonorStats.
      These are:
      <param-list>
      <param name="{lifetimeHK}">
        Number of honorable kills over lifetime.
      </param>
      <param name="{lifetimeHK}">
        Number of honorable kills over lifetime.
      </param>
      <param name="{lifetimeDK}">
        Number of dishonorable kills over lifetime.
      </param>
      <param name="{lifetimeRank}">
        Highest rank achieved over lifetime.
      </param>
      <param name="{lastweekHK}">
        Number of honorable kills earned last week.
      </param>
      <param name="{lastweekDK}">
        Number of dishonorable kills earned last week.
      </param>
      <param name="{lastweekCP}">
        Number of contribution points earned last week.
      </param>
      <param name="{lastweekStanding}">
        Numeric standing achieved last week.
      </param>
      <param name="{yesterdayHK}">
        Number of honorable kills earned yesterday.
      </param>
      <param name="{yesterdayDK}">
        Number of dishonorable kills earned yesterday.
      </param>
      <param name="{yesterdayCP}">
        Number of contribution points earned yesterday.
      </param>
      <param name="{sessionHK}">
        Number of honorable kills earned this session.
      </param>
      <param name="{sessionDK}">
        Number of dishonorable kills earned this session.
      </param>
      <param name="{currentRank}">
        Player's current rank.
      </param>
      <param name="{currentStanding}">
        Player's current numeric standing.
      </param>
      </param-list>
    </change>
    <change>
      Added two new parameters in the core addon:
      <param-list>
      <param name="{memlimitkb}">
        UI memory GC threshold, in kilobytes.
      </param>
      <param name="{memlimitmb}">
        UI memory GC threshold, in megabytes.
      </param>
      </param-list>
      Note that this isn't the total amount of memory available, but is
      instead the amount of memory that must be used before the UI runs the
      next garbage collection cycle.
    </change>
    <change>
      Reworked the tooltip to add more experience info and hopefully make it
      easier to read overall.
    </change>
    <change>
      Made the experience bars configurable, both for visibility and color.
    </change>
    <change>
      Modified the tooltip and experience bars to hide experience stats
      for level 60 characters.
    </change>
    <change>
      Added a tiny bundled addon to move the buff icons down a few pixels.
      This might be useful to players who use a wide Nox bar at the top
      of their screens.  This addon is not configurable at the moment (but
      you can easily edit the offsets in the code).
    </change>
    <change>
      Changed the "reset" slash command to reset the session instead of
      restoring defaults.  Defaults are available via a button in the config
      panel.
    </change>
    <change>
      Broke most of the remaining localization.  There wasn't much lost as
      the German translation was only partially done and the French
      translation was never done anyway.  We would welcome volunteers to
      do these translations for us.
    </change>
  </version>
  <version number="1.7" date="2005/04/27" author="Gruma">
    <change>
      Tweaked a few cosmetic issues to hopefully make the bar slightly
      more attractive.
    </change>
    <change>
      Fixed the {hours} display so that noon and midnight show as "12"
      rather than 0.
    </change>
    <change>
      Fixed the handling of rested experience so that the experience
      bars display correctly now.
    </change>
    <change>
      Made the clock offset settings configurable per-character.  This
      was needed since different realms are on different time standards.
      Unfortunately there is no "default" at this time - you have to
      configure each character separately, but only for the clock offset.
    </change>
    <change>
      Changed all bag slot calculations to ignore ammo bags.
    </change>
    <change>
      Fixed a problem with the text from slots still being displayed
      after a slot is hidden.
    </change>
    <change>
      Fixed some minor memory allocation issues.
    </change>
    <change>
      Added new variables:
      <param-list>
      <param name="{memmb}">
        UI memory used in megabytes.
      </param>
      <param name="{memkb}">
        UI memory used in kilobytes.
      </param>
      <param name="{xptolevel%}">
        Percentage XP needed to level.
      </param>
      <param name="{restbonus}">
        Amount of additional experience that will be counted as "rested".
      </param>
      <param name="{restlimit}">
        Total amount of experience needed before the "rested" bonus is used up.
      </param>
      <param name="{ammo}">
        Total amount of equipped ammo.
      </param>
      <param name="{sessionttl}">
        Estimated time to level for this session, in "0d 0h 0m 0s" format.
      </param>
      <param name="{sessionttlshort}">
        Estimated time to level for this session, in "d.h:m:s" format.
      </param>
      <param name="{levelttl}">
        Estimated time to level for this level, in "0d 0h 0m 0s" format.
      </param>
      <param name="{levelttlshort}">
        Estimated time to level for this level, in "d.h:m:s" format.
      </param>
      <param name="{bestttl}">
        Smallest of session TTL and level TTL, in "0d 0h 0m 0s" format.
      </param>
      <param name="{bestttlshort}">
        Smallest of session TTL and level TTL, in "d.h:m:s" format.
      </param>
      <param name="{allmoney}">
        Money displayed in "0g 0s 0c" format.
      </param>
      </param-list>
      The rested numbers need a little explanation.  {rest} returns
      the amount of extra bonus experience the game gives you for being
      rested.  This is half of {restbonus} which is the raw number the
      game reports.  {restlimit} is the total amount of experience that
      can be gained before the rested bonus expires, and is the same as 
      {xp} + {restbonus}.
    </change>
    <change>
      Reworked the code enough to allow extensions, and added a sample
      extension with a handful of new (probably useless) parameters:
      <param-list>
      <param name="{name}">
        Current player's name.
      </param>
      <param name="{class}">
        Current player's class.
      </param>
      <param name="{realm}">
        Current player's realm.
      </param>
      <param name="{zone}">
        Current zone the player is in.
      </param>
      <param name="{shortzone}">
        The zone name in the minimap.  Seems to be the same thing as subzone.
      </param>
      <param name="{subzone}">
        Current subzone the player is in.
      </param>
      </param-list>
    </change>
    <change>
      Added an "advanced" extension that adds a coin display to the bar.
      This is enabled by using the "{coins}" variable in the display
      string.
    </change>
  </version>
  <version number="1.6" date="2005/04/04" author="ins0mniaque">
    <change>
      Fixed the infamous rest bug. Thank you Darklynx, because I really
      don't have the time to test this out.
    </change>
  </version>
  <version number="1.5" date="2005/04/03" author="ins0mniaque">
    <change>
      Fixed German (and other languages) translation for plural based on
      code by Starmaster. Danke!
    </change>
    <change>
      *SHOULD* have fixed most maths errors. I currently do not have time
      to test it, so I used my "instinct" to correct the bugs.
    </change>
  </version>
  <version number="1.4" date="2005/04/01" author="ins0mniaque">
    <change>Added German translation provided by Wolfgang St&#x00f6;ckle. Danke sch&#x00f6;n!</change>
    <change>Changed TOC to 1300.</change>
  </version>
  <version number="1.3" date="2005/03/25" author="ins0mniaque">
    <change>
      Still an alpha release...
    </change>
    <change>
      Removed the speed display to make it work with the most recent patch.
    </change>
    <change>
      Requested feature will have to wait for me to have time to play...
    </change>
  </version>
  <version number="1.2" date="2005/03/19" author="ins0mniaque">
    <change>
      Still an alpha release...
    </change>
    <change>
      Fixed path in zip file.
    </change>
    <change>
      Fixed bug when player had no rest XP.
    </change>
    <change>
      Fixed bug that made it crash on load when language was not english.
      (Should work with french and german versions right now, but it is
      not translated, and I doubt that the dps calculator will work in
      those languages...)
    </change>
    <change>
      Added clock and tooltip parameters...
      <pre>
      New slash commands:

      /noxib tooltip [state=&lt;'on', 'off'&gt;] 
                     [position=&lt;'anchor'&gt;]
                     [x=number]
                     [y=number]
                     
      List of anchor values:
        - 'left'
        - 'topleft'
        - 'top'
        - 'topright'
        - 'right'
        - 'bottomright'
        - 'bottom'
        - 'bottomleft'
                    
      e.g. Putting the tooltip in the bottom right corner...
           /noxib tooltip position='bottomright' x=-32 y=32
           
           Shutting off the tooltip
           /noxib tooltip state='off'
           
      
      /noxib clock [offsethour=number] [offsetminute=number]
      
      e.g. Resetting the offsets to zero
           /noxib clock
           
           Putting an offset of minus 2 hours and 30 minutes
           /noxib clock offsethour=-2 offsetminute=-30
      </pre>       
    </change>
    <change>
      A complete help file is still in progress.
    </change>
    <change>
      The color parameters are still not implemented yet...
    </change>
  </version>
  <version number="1.1" date="2005/03/17" author="ins0mniaque">
    <change>
      Alpha release (to tease you all... lol).
    </change>
    <change>
      Nearly a complete rewrite of the bar.
    </change>
    <change>
      Localization has been "lost". Will be relocalized when beta version
      goes out. Sorry for the delay.
    </change>
    <change>
      Fixed bug with rest xp showing in bar.
    </change>
    <change>
      Has now 9 completly customizable slots.
    </change>
    <change>
      The Clock, Tooltip and Colors parameters are not implemented yet
      (but they are listed in help).
    </change>
    <change>
      Now uses a modified version of the FlexBar Slash Command Parser.
    </change>
    <change>
      Now has a key binding for toggling visibility.
    </change>
    <change>
      Rapid listing of slash commands:
      <pre>
      "Table" parameters values notes:
        - numbers -> "slot=1"
        - ranges  -> "slot=1-6"
        - tables  -> "slot=[ 1 3 7 8 ]"
      
      Commands:
      
        Troubleshooting:
          /noxib reset -> Resets the bar and slots
      
        Visibility:
          /noxib show   [slot=table] -> Shows bar/slots
          /noxib hide   [slot=table] -> Hides bar/slots
          /noxib toggle [slot=table] -> Toggles bar/slots
      
          e.g. /noxib show slot=4-6 -> Mark slots 4, 5 and 6 as visible.
      
        Locking:
          /noxib lock   -> Lock the bar
          /noxib unlock -> Unlocks the bar
          
        Slots:
          /noxib resize slot=table width=number -> Resizes slots to 
                                                   specified width.
          /noxib remap slot=table display='string' -> Remaps slots to 
                                                      specified display 
                                                      string.
                                                      
          Display strings:
            Displays string (enclosed in single quotes) defines what
            each slot will display. Variables (enclosed withing braces)
            will be replaced in the bar with the current value.
            
            e.g. '{framerate} fps' will display the current framerate,
                 followed by a space and then "fps".
                 
                 
      </pre>                 
      
      List of variables (yep, there is a whole lot) :
      <param-list>      
      <param name="{latency}">
        Latency in milliseconds (Lag)
      </param>
      <param name="{framerate}">
        Framerate (fps)
      </param>
      <param name="{24hours}">
        Hours in current time in military format.
      </param>
      <param name="{hours}">
        Hours in current time.
      </param>
      <param name="{minutes}">
        Minutes in current time.
      </param>
      <param name="{ampm}">
        AM or PM of current time.
      </param>
      <param name="{speed}">
        Travelling speed in percentage.
      </param>
      <param name="{x}">
        Current horizontal map location.
      </param>
      <param name="{y}">
        Current vertical map location.
      </param>
      <param name="{money}">
        Current total amount of money (in copper).
      </param>
      <param name="{gold}">
        Current amount of gold.
      </param>
      <param name="{silver}">
        Current amount of silver.
      </param>
      <param name="{copper}">
        Current amount of copper.
      </param>
      <param name="{hpregen}">
        Current health regeneration rate.
      </param>
      <param name="{manaregen}">
        Current mana regeneration rate.
      </param>
      <param name="{hp}">
        Current health.
      </param>
      <param name="{hploss}">
        Current health loss (max - current).
      </param>
      <param name="{hp%}">
        Current health percentage.
      </param>
      <param name="{maxhp}">
        Maximum health.
      </param>
      <param name="{mana}">
        Current mana.
      </param>
      <param name="{manaloss}">
        Current mana loss (max - current).
      </param>
      <param name="{mana%}">
        Current mana percentage.
      </param>
      <param name="{maxmana}">
        Current mana loss (max - current).
      </param>
      <param name="{xp}">
        Current XP.
      </param>
      <param name="{xptolevel}">
        XP to reach next level.
      </param>
      <param name="{xp%}">
        Current XP percentage of next level.
      </param>
      <param name="{maxxp}">
        Total XP to get to next level.
      </param>
      <param name="{rest}">
        Amount of rest XP.
      </param>
      <param name="{level}">
        Current level.
      </param>
      <param name="{ubs}">
        Used bag slots.
      </param>
      <param name="{abs}">
        Available bag slots.
      </param>
      <param name="{tbs}">
        Total bag slots.
      </param>
      </param-list>      
      
      For current combat (or last combat) :
      <param-list>      
      <param name="{dps}">
        Damage per second.
      </param>
      <param name="{hps}">
        Healing per second.
      </param>
      <param name="{petdps}">
        Pet damage per second.
      </param>
      <param name="{totaldamage}">
        Total damage.
      </param>
      <param name="{totalheal}">
        Total healing.
      </param>
      <param name="{combatduration}">
        Combat duration.
      </param>
      <param name="{meleehits}">
        Number of melee hits.
      </param>
      <param name="{meleemisses}">
        Number of melee misses.
      </param>
      <param name="{meleecrits}">
        Number of melee critical hits.
      </param>
      <param name="{meleehits%}">
        Percentage of melee hits.
      </param>
      <param name="{meleemisses%}">
        Percentage of melee misses.
      </param>
      <param name="{meleecrits%}">
        Percentage of melee critical hits.
      </param>
      <param name="{nonmeleehits}">
        Number of non-melee hits.
      </param>
      <param name="{nonmeleemisses}">
        Number of non-melee misses.
      </param>
      <param name="{nonmeleecrits}">
        Number of non-melee critical hits.
      </param>
      <param name="{nonmeleehits%}">
        Percentage of non-melee hits.
      </param>
      <param name="{nonmeleemisses%}">
        Percentage of non-melee misses.
      </param>
      <param name="{nonmeleecrits%}">
        Percentage of non-melee critical hits.
      </param>
      <param name="{healhits}">
        Number of successful heals.
      </param>
      <param name="{healmisses}">
        Number of failed heals.
      </param>
      <param name="{healcrits}">
        Number of critical heals.
      </param>
      <param name="{healhits%}">
        Percentage of successful heals.
      </param>
      <param name="{healmisses%}">
        Percentage of failed heals.
      </param>
      <param name="{healcrits%}">
        Percentage of critical heals.
      </param>
      </param-list>  
            And for color:
      <pre>            
            |caarrggbb         -> aa = Hexadecimal display of alpha value
                               -> rr = Hexadecimal display of red value
                               -> gg = Hexadecimal display of green value
                               -> bb = Hexadecimal display of blue value
        
            |r                 -> Restore previous color
            
            e.g. '|cffff0000{dps}|r dps' will display the current dps in
                 opaque red (ff, ff, 00, 00), and then " dps" in the 
                 default color (which is a nearly pure yellow).
      </pre>           
      Quick exemples:
      <pre>  
        Display only clock (in white) in a 100 pixel large bar:
        
          /noxib hide slot=1-9           -> Hide all slots
          /noxib show slot=1             -> Show slot 1
          /noxib resize slot=1 width=100 -> Resize slot 1 to 100 pixels
          /noxib remap slot=1 display='|cffffffff{24hours}:{minutes}'
      </pre>      
    </change>
    <change>
      A complete help file in progress.
    </change>
  </version>
  <version number="1.0" date="2005/03/07" author="ins0mniaque">
    <change>
      First version.
    </change>
    <change>
      Usage is quite obvious, type /noxib for more information.
    </change>
  </version>
</changelog>